reagan.com 2016-06-24

# @Reagan.com secure email address - Ronald Reagan email address. Privacy policy

**Reagan.com Website Privacy Statement**

This website is a service of Reagan.com, LLC (hereinafter referred to as “ **Reagan.com** ”, “ **we** ”, “ **us** ”, or “ **our** ”).  We provide this statement to identify for you the privacy practices that we adhere to with respect to this website, including an explanation of: (1) the categories of personally identifiable information about you that may be collected and the choices available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of the information; (2) how the information is used and the categories of persons or entities with whom the information may be shared; (3) how you can opt in or out of Reagan.com promotional e-mail; (4) the kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information; (5) how you can review and request changes to the information; (6) how we notify visitors and users of this website of changes to this privacy statement; and (7) the privacy policies that apply to subscribers to Reagan.com products and services. 

Questions regarding Reagan.com’s website privacy statement should be directed to [support@reagan.com](mailto:support@reagan.com).  Or by mail to Reagan.com, 230 S. Clark Street, Suite 302, Chicago, IL 60604. 

**Collection of Information**

The information collected by Reagan.com falls into two categories: (1) information voluntarily supplied by visitors to and users of the website and (2) tracking information recorded as visitors and users navigate through the website.  Some of this information is personally identifiable information, but much of it is not. Personally identifiable information is information that identifies a particular person. 

As a general policy, Reagan.com does not automatically collect “personal” information from visitors to this website.  However, certain non-personal information of visitors is recorded by the standard operation of the Reagan.com Service.  We use so-called “cookies,” which are small files stored on a computer's hard drive to simplify and improve a user’s Web experience.  The cookie does not personally identify you.  Our website may store information in a cookie about your computer configuration so that it can more efficiently provide information to you the next time you visit the site.  Or, your browser program might save a cookie with your username and password so that a website's server will automatically recognize you the next time you access the site. 

Generally, information tracked by our system includes the type of browser being used by the visitor, the type of operating system in use by the visitor and the domain name of the visitor's Internet service provider.  By having this information, Web pages optimized for a particular visitor's computer are automatically made available to that visitor.  We may also use aggregate, non-personally identifiable information to determine the number of visitors to this website and to determine which products and services are the most popular with our website visitors. 

We may also use one or more advertising network providers to help present advertisements or other content on this website.  These advertising network providers use cookies, web beacons, or other technologies to serve you advertisements or content tailored to interests you have shown by browsing on this and other websites you have visited.  Advertising network providers collect non-personally identifiable information such as your browser type, your operating system, web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other click stream data. 

The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by these advertising network providers is subject to their own privacy policies, not our privacy policy for this website or its Service.  If you do not want the benefits of this advertising, you may opt-out by visiting [ww.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp).

In addition to the information that is collected by our system, you may also voluntarily provide to Reagan.com when you visit certain areas of this website personal information about yourself, such as your name, address, email address, and other information that may personally identify you.  Although this information is not generally required by Reagan.com for you to use this website, Reagan.com may be unable to provide you with some products and services that we make available to other visitors to our website without the information.  You also will not be able to order selected products or services over the Reagan.com website unless you provide certain personally identifying information about yourself.  The information you supply will help us to offer you more personalized features, to tailor our website to your interests and make it more useful to you.  Our system will remember some of this information the next time you login to our secure eCommerce section and use our website, but can be changed later by you. 

Reagan.com is especially concerned with children who access and use this website.  Reagan.com does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen.  If Reagan.com (or any other website operator) collects personal information from children under the age of thirteen, we must first obtain parental consent.  Children should always get permission from their parents before sending any information about themselves over the Internet.  Reagan.com strongly encourages parents to supervise their children’s online activities and consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers that help control access to certain content on the Internet.  These tools can also help prevent children from disclosing online personal information without parental permission. 

 **Use and Sharing of Information**

Reagan.com will generally use any personally identifiable data that you provide to us when you visit this site only for the purposes described at the time it is collected and otherwise to contact you to make you aware of other products and services that you may find of interest.  We consider the personally identifiable information contained in our business records to be confidential.  We may sometimes disclose personally identifiable information about you to our affiliates or to others who work for us, as necessary to provide our Services to you.  We may be required by law or legal process to disclose certain personally identifiable information about you without your consent and without notice in order to comply with a valid legal process such as a subpoena, court order, or search warrant. 

 **Links to Other Websites**

This website may contain links to or from other websites whose privacy policies and practices we do not control. You should carefully review the privacy policies and practices of each such site in order to determine how each site may use any personal information you provide. 

 **Security**

All information gathered on our website is stored within a database that is designed to be accessible only to Reagan.com and its specifically authorized contractors and vendors.  Although Reagan.com implements security measures to protect from disclosure or interception any such personally identifiable information that you may voluntarily supply to us, we cannot guarantee in all instances the complete security of such information.  

 **Changes to Information**

You may review and change information that you provide to us through this website by returning to the pages where you entered it, and reviewing or changing the information directly. You may also request changes to some information, such as billing and account information, by sending an email to support@reagan.com, if you are able to verify your identity using a Reagan.com username, secret question and answer, or another identifier requested by Reagan.com. 

 **Changes to this Privacy Statement**

We may change this privacy statement from time to time, so please check this statement periodically when you visit this website. If we change this privacy statement at some point in the future, we will post the changes on our website. By continuing to use the website after we post any changes, you accept and agree to the most recent version of the Reagan.com privacy statement. 

(Revised as of January 10, 2012)

* * *

 **ACCEPTABLE USE, EMAIL RETENTION AND COPYRIGHT POLICIES**

In the Acceptable Use Policy, Email Retention Policy and Copyright Policy (each the " **Policy** " as applicable, and collectively, the “ **Service Policies** ”), we refer to Reagan.com, LLC as "Reagan.com", "we", "us" or "our", and users of the Reagan.com website and services provided by Reagan.com, and, as applicable, all associated media, printed materials, and “online” or electronic documentation (collectively, the “ **Service(s)** ”), as the "Customer", "you" or "your."  The purpose of the Service Policies is to ensure that the Services are used in a manner that benefits everyone.  In order to use the Reagan.com Service, you must read, understand and agree to abide by these Service Policies.  

WE MAY REVISE, AMEND OR RESTATE THE SERVICE POLICIES FROM TIME TO TIME BY POSTING A NEW VERSION OF ON THE REAGAN.COM WEB SITE AT WWW.REAGAN.COM (OR ANY SUCCESSOR URL(S)).  REVISED, AMENDED OR RESTATED SERVICE POLICIES ARE EFFECTIVE IMMEDIATELY UPON POSTING.  ACCORDINGLY, CUSTOMERS AND USERS SHOULD REGULARLY VISIT OUR WEB SITE AND REVIEW THE SERVICE POLICIES TO ENSURE THAT THEIR ACTIVITIES CONFORM TO THE MOST RECENT VERSIONS.

 ** _Acceptable Use Policy_**

A.         Customers must use the Service in a manner that is ethical and in conformance with prevailing community standards.  Reagan.com shall have the sole and non-reviewable right to determine whether a Customer's use violates this standard.

B.         Customers must use the Service in a manner that respects the integrity of our system and all components thereof.  Customers will not use or allow others to use the Service to disrupt our network or equipment, or equipment owned by other Reagan.com customers.  For example, Customers agree not to: (i) use or allow others to use the Service to disrupt other Internet Service Providers' service, including but not limited to by e-mail bombing or the use of mass mailing programs; (ii) access or attempt to access other users' systems; (iii) disrupt others' use of the network; (iv) damage or change our or other users' computer hardware or software in any way, whether directly or indirectly.

D.         Customers shall not use the Service, directly or indirectly, for any unlawful purpose.  Customers shall not post, store, disseminate or transmit through the Service any information, data or material (including any message or series of messages) that violates or infringes in any way upon the rights of others (including copyright, trademark or other intellectual property rights), that is unlawful, threatening, abusive, obstructive, harassing, libelous, invasive of privacy or publicity rights, or in the circumstances would be obscene, pornographic or indecent, constitutes hate speech or is otherwise objectionable, offensive, embarrassing, distressing, vulgar, hateful, racially or ethnically offensive, or otherwise inappropriate (regardless of whether this material or its dissemination is unlawful), or that encourages conduct that would constitute a criminal offense, give rise to civil liability or otherwise violate any law.  Reagan.com shall have the sole and unreviewable right to determine whether content violates these standards.

E.         Customers shall not resell or otherwise offer or make the Service available to other users, locations or tenants, and shall not charge others to use the Service, in whole or in part, directly or indirectly, or on a bundled or unbundled basis.  Customers are specifically prohibited from permitting other users and/or locations to access the Reagan.com Internet service, whether through wireless or other means.  Without limiting the generality of the foregoing, and except as otherwise specifically provided in a written agreement between Customer and Reagan.com, the Service is for personal and non-commercial use only and Customer agrees not to use the Service for operation as an Internet service provider, a server site for ftp, telnet, rlogin, e-mail hosting, "web hosting" or other similar applications, for any business enterprise, or as an end-point on a local area network or wide area network.

F.         Customers shall not utilize excessive "bandwidth" (i.e. volume of data transmitted or received) at any time or on an on-going basis.  Reagan.com shall have the sole and unreviewable right to determine whether Customer's use violates this standard.  Customers must ensure that their activity does not improperly restrict, inhibit, or degrade any other user's use of the Service, nor represent (in the sole judgment of Reagan.com) an unusually large burden on the website.  In addition, Customers must ensure that their activities do not improperly restrict, inhibit, disrupt, degrade or impede Reagan.com's ability to deliver the Service or monitor the Service, and/or other network Services.  

G.         Customers may not use the Service for spamming.  This includes but is not limited to the following activities:

  * Sending bulk unsolicited messages
  * Sending e-mails which provoke complaints from the recipients
  * Sending junk email
  * Using distribution lists that include people who have not given their permission to be included in such a distribution process
  * Posting commercial ads to Usenet groups that do not permit them
  * Posting articles that contain binary encoded data to non-binary newsgroups
  * Sending excessive and repeated off-topic messages to newsgroups
  * Sending excessive and repeated cross-postings
  * Harassing other Internet users including but not limited to transmitting any threatening, libelous or obscene materials.
  * Posting or transmitting charity requests, petitions for signatures, chain letters or letters relating to pyramid schemes or contests, or any other duplicative or unsolicited messages (commercial or otherwise).
  * Posting or transmitting through the Service any material that constitutes or contains advertising or any solicitation with respect to products or service.

H.         Activities that have the effect of facilitating unsolicited commercial e-mail or unsolicited bulk e-mail, whether or not the e-mail is commercial in nature, are prohibited.

I.          Customers will not use, nor allow others to use, the Service to intentionally transmit computer "viruses," worms, "Trojan horses" or other harmful software programs and Customer will use Customer's best efforts to prevent the unintentional transmission of such viruses or other harmful software.

J.          Customers will not impersonate another user, falsify one's user name, age or identity in e-mail or in any post or transmission to any newsgroup or mailing list or other similar groups or lists.  Customers will not forge any message header of any electronic transmission, originating or passing through the Service, or perform any other similar fraudulent activity.

K.         Customers must respect the property rights of others, including those conferred by copyright, trademark and other laws that protect intellectual property rights. Except as allowed by applicable law, Customers shall not upload, post or otherwise make available on the Service any material protected by copyright, trademark, or trade secret or other proprietary right without the express permission of the owner thereof. Customers may upload public domain materials and is responsible for and assumes all risks with respect to the determination of whether materials are in the public domain.

L.         Except as expressly permitted under copyright law, no copying, redistribution, publication or commercial exploitation of downloaded material will be permitted without the express prior written consent of Reagan.com and, where applicable, the third party copyright owner. In the event of any permitted copying, redistribution or publication of copyrighted material, no changes in or deletion of author attribution or copyright notice shall be made.

M.        Customers will not access any other person's computer or computer system, software, or data without their knowledge and consent; breach the security of another user; or attempt to circumvent the user authentication or security of any host, network, or account. This includes, but is not limited to, accessing data not intended for Customer, logging into or making use of a server or account Customer are not expressly authorized to access, or probing the security of other hosts, networks, or accounts.

N.         Customers will not use or distribute tools designed or used for compromising security, such as password guessing programs, decoders, password gatherers, analyzers, cracking tools, packet sniffers, encryption circumvention devices, or Trojan Horse programs.  Unauthorized port scanning, for any reason, is strictly prohibited.

O.        Customers will not restrict, inhibit, interfere with, or otherwise disrupt or cause a performance degradation, regardless of intent, purpose or knowledge, to the Service or any Reagan.com (or Reagan.com supplier) host, server, backbone network, node or service, or otherwise cause a performance degradation to any Reagan.com facilities used to deliver the Service.

P.         Customers will not distribute programs that remove locks or time-outs built into software (cracks).

Q.        Customers will not initiate, perpetuate, or in any way participate in any pyramid or other illegal soliciting scheme.

R.         Customers will not participate in the collection of e-mail addresses, screen names, or other identifiers of others (without their prior consent), a practice sometimes known as spidering or harvesting, or participate in the use of software (including "spyware") designed to facilitate this activity.

S.         Customers will not collect responses from unsolicited messages.

T.         Customers will not collect, or attempt to collect, personal information about third parties without their consent.

U.         Customers will not interfere with computer networking or telecommunications service to any user, host or network, including, without limitation, denial of service attacks, flooding of a network, overloading a service, improper seizing and abuse of operator privileges and attempts to "crash" a host.

V.         Customers are fully responsible for their account and responsible for any misuse of the Service, even if the misuse was committed by a friend, family member, or guest with access to Customer's account. Customers are solely responsible for the security of any device they chooses to connect to the Service, including any data stored or shared on that device.

W.        Messages posted to newsgroups must comply with the written charters or FAQs for those newsgroups as well as any other terms and conditions applicable to any particular newsgroups or provider of newsgroups.  Advertisements, solicitations, or other commercial messages should be posted only in those newsgroups whose charters or FAQs explicitly permit them.  Customers are responsible for determining the policies of a given newsgroup before posting to it.  Reagan.com reserves the right to discontinue access to any newsgroup at any time for any reason.

X.         Customers are solely responsible for any information or content that they or others publish or store at Reagan.com.  Reagan.com reserves the right to remove, block, or refuse to post or store any information or materials, in whole or in part, that it, in its sole discretion, deem to be offensive, indecent, or otherwise inappropriate regardless of whether this material or its dissemination is unlawful.

 ** _Email Retention Policy_**

 **General Policy**

Reagan.com reserves the right to manage its network for the greatest benefit of the greatest number of users and subscribers including, without limitation, the following: rate limiting, rejection or removal of "spam" or otherwise unsolicited bulk email, anti-virus mechanisms, traffic prioritization, and protocol filtering.  You expressly accept that such action on the part of Reagan.com may affect the performance of the Service. Reagan.com reserves the right to enforce limits on specific features of the Service including, without limitation, email storage (including deletion of dormant or unchecked email).

 **Email**

Email boxes |   
---|---  
  
Size of mail boxes

| 

10 GB per email mailbox  
  
Maximum attachment size

| 

50MB  
  
 **Message rules**

| 

 **Action**

| 

 **Timing**  
  
---|---|---  
  
Inbox

| |   
  
     Read

| 

Delete

| 

Delete at time of account deactivation  
  
     Unread 

| 

Delete

| 

Delete at time of account deactivation  
  
Drafts

| 

Delete

| 

Delete at time of account deactivation  
  
Junk Folder

| 

Delete

| 

Delete at time of account deactivation  
  
Trash

| 

Delete

| 

Delete at time of account deactivation  
  
Sent

| 

Leave message on server

| 

On by default  
  
Sent that is on server

| 

Delete

| 

Delete at time of account deactivation  
  
Rate limiting for webmail

| 

200 recipients max

| 

200 messages/hr max  
  
Rate limiting for Outlook

| 

1000 recipients max

| 

1000 messages/hr max  
  
 ** _DMCA Policy and Procedure for Making Claims of Copyright Infringement_**

Reagan.com requires that all Customers and users of the Service comply with U.S. copyright and related laws.  It is our policy to comply with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (the " **DMCA** ") and other applicable laws to reserve the right to terminate in appropriate circumstances the Service provided to any customer or user who is either found to infringe third party copyright or other intellectual property rights, including repeat infringers, or who Reagan.com believes in its sole discretion is infringing these rights.  Reagan.com may terminate the Service at any time with or without notice for any affected customer or user.  These policies do not affect any other rights Reagan.com may have under law or contract.

Owners of copyrighted works who believe that their rights under U.S. copyright law have been infringed may take advantage of certain provisions of the DMCA to report alleged infringements.  You may file a notification of claimed infringement pursuant to the DMCA (a “ **Notification** ”) with the Designated Agent of Reagan.com if you believe that your rights under U.S. copyright law (See Title 17, United States Code, Section 512(c)(3)) have been violated.  The DMCA provides the following procedure for parties to follow who wish to file a Notification of claimed infringement with Reagan.com.  To serve a Notification on Reagan.com, send your Notification to:

Email Address of Designated Agent: support@reagan.com 

**Contents of Notification  **

In order to be effective under the DMCA, the Notification must (i) be in writing, and (ii) provided to the Designated Agent of Reagan.com.  In order for such a complaint to be effective under the DMCA, the Notification must include the following:

  1. A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.
  2. Identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed, or, if multiple copyrighted works at a single online site are covered by a single Notification, a representative list of such works at that site.
  3. Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity and that is to be removed or access to which is to be disabled, and information reasonably sufficient to permit the service provider to locate the material.
  4. Information reasonably sufficient to permit the service provider to contact the complaining party, such as an address, telephone number, and if available, an electronic mail address at which the complaining party may be contacted.
  5. A statement that the complaining party has a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law.
  6. A statement that the information in the Notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that the complaining party is authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.

Upon receipt of the written Notification containing the information described in 1 through 6 above, Reagan.com will, in accordance with applicable law:

  1. Remove or disable access to the material that is alleged to be infringing; and
  2. Take reasonable steps to promptly notify the subscriber that it has removed or disabled access to the material.

NOTE: Under the DMCA, claimants who make misrepresentations concerning copyright infringement may be liable for damages incurred as a result of the removal or blocking of the material, court costs, and attorneys fees. See Title 17, United States Code, Section 512(d).

NOTE: The information provided regarding the DMCA is for informational purposes only, and is not intended as legal advice.  If you believe your rights under U.S. Copyright law have been infringed, you should consult an attorney.

 **Violation of Service Policies**

If a Customer (or any user of a Customer's account) uses the Service in a way that Reagan.com, in its sole discretion, believes violates our Service Policies, Reagan.com may take any responsive actions that it deems appropriate, including temporary or permanent removal of content, temporary or permanent blocking of websites, and the immediate suspension or termination of all or any portion of the Service.  Reagan.com and its agents will have no liability for any these responsive actions.

Reagan.com further reserves the right to investigate suspected violations of its policies. Customers expressly authorize Reagan.com to cooperate with (i) law enforcement authorities in the investigation of suspected legal violations, and (ii) system administrators at other Internet service providers or other network or computing facilities in order to enforce this Policy.  This cooperation may include: (i) Reagan.com providing available personally identifiable information about Customer to law enforcement or system administrators, including, but not limited to, user name, subscriber name, and other account information; and (ii) temporary or permanent blocking of certain websites.  Upon termination of a Customer's account, Reagan.com is authorized to delete any files, programs, data and e-mail messages associated with a Customer's account.

 **Limitation of Liability**

Notwithstanding anything contained in these Service Policies (as they may be amended or restated from time to time), Reagan.com and its suppliers reserve the right at all times to delete a customer's email, files, or other information that is stored on Reagan.com's or its suppliers' servers or systems.  Customers understand and agree that Reagan.com shall have no liability whatsoever as a result of the loss or removal of any such email, files, or other information.

CUSTOMERS AGREE TO INDEMNIFY, DEFEND AND HOLD HARMLESS REAGAN.COM AND ITS AFFILIATES, SUPPLIERS, AND AGENTS AGAINST ALL CLAIMS AND EXPENSES (INCLUDING REASONABLE ATTORNEY FEES) RESULTING FROM CUSTOMERS’ ENGAGING IN ANY OF THE PROHIBITED ACTIVITIES LISTED IN THIS POLICY OR RESULTING FROM CUSTOMERS’ VIOLATION OF THE POLICY OR OF ANY OTHER POSTED REAGAN.COM POLICY RELATED TO THE SERVICE. 

(Revision Date: January 10, 2012)
